{
    "Game": {
        "Boston": {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Fenway Park is the oldest ballpark in Major League Baseball. In which year was it built?",
                    "options": [
                        "1905",
                        "1912",
                        "1922",
                        "1928"
                    ],
                    "id" : "0",
                    "correct" : "1912"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which one of these is not a Boston sports team?",
                    "options": [
                        "Bruins",
                        "Celtics",
                        "White Sox",
                        "Red Sox"
                    ],
                    "id": "1",
                    "correct" : "White Sox"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Paul Revere’s ride was sparked by two lanterns in which Boston steeple?",
                    "options": [
                        "Old North Church",
                        "Trinity Church",
                        "Cathedral Church of St. Paul",
                        "King’s Chapel"
                    ],
                    "id": "2",
                    "correct" : "Old North Church"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Harvard University is the oldest institution of higher education in the United States. When was it founded?",
                    "options": [
                        "1602",
                        "1636",
                        "1650",
                        "1685"
                    ],
                    "id": "3",
                    "correct" : "1636"
                },
                {
                    "question": "The Boston subway lines are named after:",
                    "options": [
                        "Colors",
                        "Numbers",
                        "Letters",
                        "Historic figures"
                    ],
                    "id": "4",
                    "correct" : "Colors"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which of these movies was not filmed in Boston?",
                    "options": [
                        "The Boondock Saints",
                        "The Departed",
                        "The Town",
                        "Deadpool"
                    ],
                    "id": "5",
                    "correct" : "Deadpool"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which of these bands is originally from Boston?",
                    "options": [
                        "Aerosmith",
                        "The Rolling Stones",
                        "Guns N’ Roses",
                        "AC/DC"
                    ],
                    "id": "6",
                    "correct" : "Aerosmith"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which of these is the official dessert of Massachusetts?",
                    "options": [
                        "Fig Newton",
                        "Boston Cream Pie",
                        "Mike’s Cannoli",
                        "Salt Water Taffy"
                    ],
                    "id": "7",
                    "correct" : "Boston Cream Pie"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which of these is illegal in Boston?",
                    "options": [
                        "Pub Crawl",
                        "Trolley Tour",
                        "Happy Hour",
                        "Candlepin Bowling"
                    ],
                    "id": "8",
                    "correct" : "Happy Hour"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where does the Boston nickname “Beantown” come from?",
                    "options": [
                        "Drinking Coffee and Coffee Beans",
                        "Farming and Green Beans",
                        "Molasses Trade and Baked Beans",
                        "The story of Jack and the Beanstalk"
                    ],
                    "id": "9",
                    "correct" : "Molasses Trade and Baked Beans"
                }
            ]
        }
    }
}